# Hussain Radhi Marzooq

# <u>Hussain.marzooq.bh@icloud.com</u> - +971588988449 UAE – Dubai

# **Professional Summery**

Competent human resources professional, CIPD member and Extensively Experienced Human Resource Manager with more than 8 years' experience, in recruiting and staffing, monitoring turnover and retention, and company compliance. Desire to apply knowledge of the industry to assist in all HR related needs and strategic goals.

Multi skilled life coach with experience in dealing with people's behavior and psychology, Languages teacher, Photographer, blogger and writer.

In continues process of learning swift, IOS and web development, with the aim to learn other programing languages.

#### **Skills**

- Coaching, Leading & inspiring
- Developing
- Team work and collaborative
- Capability of fast learning and adapt to changes
- Working under pressures
- Event Management
- Ms.Office Advance
- Excel and formulas Expert

## CONTACT DETAILS

Portfolio: https://immortality00.github.io/hussain.marzooq/

GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/immortality00">https://github.com/immortality00</a>

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/immortality00">https://www.linkedin.com/in/immortality00</a>

Photography - Instagram : @The.3.eye

### Work Experience

# Freelancing - HR Consultant

Bahrain - January 2016 - Present

# Garden Scape Landscape Contracting - HR & Admin Manager

Bahrain - April 2015 until June 2015

Handling and managing:

- The Employee Relations
- Recruitments process
- Training,
- Performance Management,
- Learning & Development
- Payroll,
- Salaries & benefits.
- HR budgets,
- Reports and Analysis.

- Creating the HR Department from the scratch
- Preparing and implementing The Policy & Procedures.

# Imervs Al Zavani Fused Minerals - HR Officer

Bahrain - August 2014 until April 2015

Handling and Managing:

- The Employee Relations
- Recruitments process
- Training,
- Performance Management,
- Learning & Development
- Payroll, Salaries & benefits.
- HR budgets, Reports and Analysis
- Employees database and records

- Leading and directing the Human Resource team to deliver a comprehensive HR services
- Supporting the Managing Director in the policy & procedures preparing and implementation.

## National Concrete Company - Payroll Officer & HR Coordinator

Bahrain - October 2011 To August 2014

Supporting the HR manager in:

- Budget planing,
- Recruitment process.
- MIS
- Training and development plan
- Developing the HR practices and procedures .
- Implementing new software for the company

Managing and handling:

- Payroll
- Reports
- Contracts, letters, and forms
- Monitoring and training the department team

Supporting The HR team in:

- Employees relations
- Administration
- Invoices clearances

### Havelock AHI - HR Officer

Bahrain - October 2007- May 2011

Handling and maintaining:

- Payroll
- Administration / HR Reports.
- Administration / HR Budget
- All the invoices related to Administration, HR and employee fees
- Employees, details, training, files, leaves and vacations
- Immigration, Ministries, Embassies and visas, Staffs/workers transports, drivers, administration expenses.

- Coordinating with The Company Branches in GCC for all Administration/HR related.
- Assisting in events managements

# Languages

Arabic & English .. Learning Russian - Very Beginner Level

# **Education**

	Astrolab Web Development		Dubai	2018	
	London Brewery	Swift & IOS Development	Udemy – online	2018	
	CIPD	Diploma in Human Resources Practice	UK	2014	
	Victory Training Institute	CIPD Lvl 3 – Foundation, A Diploma L&D	Bahrain	2014	
	Horizons HRD	Personal & Professional Development Skills Throw NLP		Bahrain	2011
	Bisan Institute of Hospitality Management	Certificate of Achievement in Hospital Course	Bahrain	2004	
	Certificates				
	Harvest Training Center	The Art and Science of Value Based Decision Making		Bahrain	2014
	Harvest Training Center Coaching for Effective Leadership			Bahrain	2014
	Logic Institute	Effective Business Emails		Bahrain	2013
	Additional Experie	nce			
	GM Assistant	Party Hostel	Georgia	January 18 – April 2018	
	English Teacher	CPAT Languages School	Egypt	Feb 17 – Decem	ber 2017
	English Teacher	AIESEC – St Petersburg	Russia	March 2016	
	Life Coach & Consultant	Freelancing	Worldwide	April 2013 – Present	
	Marshal	Bahrain Motorsports Marshal Club & Motor Federation	Bahrain	2004 – 2010	
Secretary AL Ghadeer Graphi		AL Ghadeer Graphics	Bahrain	August 2007 – September 2007	
	Sales Man	Al Sorror Bahrain		2006 – Summer Job	
	Customer service Home Center – Marina Mall Bahrain		Bahrain	2006 – Summer Job	
	Refrences				

Zahra AL Qassab	HR Manager	+97339002622	Zahra.Alqassab@rma-rheinau.de
Zainab Abdulla	HR Manager	+97333993665	Zainab@nccbahrain.com
M V Raju	Sr. Business support	+97317832029	Raju@havelockahi.biz
Moh'd Imran	HR Manager	+97333118679	